<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>title</title>
    <link>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on title</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {2020}</copyright><atom:link href="https://hkhajanchi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 19:59:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Khajanchi, H., Bruno, J., Adegbege, A. (2020). A Real-Time Architecture for Embedded Model Predictive Control International Federation of Automatic Control World Congress
Khajanchi, H., Bezold, J., Kilcher, M., et. al (2019). PSIG-GAN: A Parameterized Synthetic Image Generator Optimized via Non-Differentiable GAN IEEE Applied Imagery and Pattern Recognition Workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 19:29:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Bitwidth Speculation
Ongoing
Northwestern University
Advised by Dr. Simone Campanoni and Dr. Russ Joseph
 Profiling register allocation in a compiler-architecture co-design for timing-speculative/bitwidth-speculative tiny devices  Analog Solvers for Real-time Model Predictive Control
September 2019
The College of New Jersey
Advised by Dr. Ambrose Adegbege
 Helped develop MATLAB simulations for comparing different continuous-time quadratic programming solvers  Hardware Acceleration for AI-based Hearing Aids
Ongoing
Illinois Institute of Technology &amp;amp; Northwestern University</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 19:25:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/education/</guid>
      <description>Ph.D. Computer Engineering, Northwestern University
Expected: 2025
Advised by Simone Campanoni
B.S Electrical Engineering, The College of New Jersey
2020
GPA 3.69
Graduated Cum Laude</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 14:07:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hkhajanchi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a first year Computer Engineering PhD student at Northwestern University advised by Prof. Simone Campanoni. My research interests are at the intersection of compilers and computer architecture, specifically for resource-constrained environments. I did my undergrad in Electrical Engineering at The College of New Jersey, where I did some research in embedded control and deep learning.
Outside of the lab, I enjoy playing ice hockey, lifting weights, skiing, running and playing tennis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
